[Kim Hyeonseo as Sung Ho]
[Jung Myeongcheol as Yoo Sehyun]
[Kim Seonghyuk as Kwon Hyukjae]
[Jung Hyunwoong as Kim Minho]
[Sin and Love]
[Episode 7]
Sehyun,
how many years
have you been working for me?
Five years.
That's right.
It's been 5 years.
I've been feeding you
for the past 5 years.
And how dare you
mess up my business like this?
Hyung,
I did everything you ordered.
Then why are the police
always investigating Gangnam Palace?
That can't be.
It's all over.
Over?
Did you know
that Sung Ho started investigating
the drug case a few years ago?
He even investigated
Gangnam Palace himself!
Hey.
You're in cahoots with him, aren't you?
Whatever.
Let's end this all.
Open your eyes.
'Cause I don't want to kill you yet.
Sung Ho...
will come to save me.
Is that so?
Great.
Then I'll kill you both.
Just kill me.
I can't do that.
You can't die right now.
Because Sung Ho will come to save you.
Kwon Hyukjae!
Sung Ho.
Don't move.
Sung Ho,
you better think carefully.
Don't you want to save Yoo Sehyun?
That's right.
You found this place
faster than I expected.
Let Sehyun go.
Did you come alone?
Yes.
No backup?
I came alone.
Hey.
Sung Ho, you're so arrogant.
Okay.
You found this place by yourself—
that's impressive.
But coming alone is basically suicide.
Sung Ho,
do you know where this is?
A place where you can do
whatever you want, right?
Right.
This is my territory.
My territory
with no CCTV and no one around.
No one would know if someone died here.
That's right.
It means no one would know
if someone died.
You
have been investigating me
for a long time, haven't you?
So what did you find out?
Gangnam Palace's
dirty money has been laundered
into clean money.
You made Sehyun keep the ledger
so he could take the blame.
Hey.
Do you know why you can't apprehend me?
Because you're inhuman.
No.
It's because you're tracking me down.
Me?
You're tracking me down,
so I'm being more careful.
No one can catch me when I'm careful.
Ultimately, you can't escape
from my grasp either.
Hey, damn it.
Relax, you rascal.
Okay.
Let's not talk about work
and talk about something else.
Do you like him?
That's why you came here?
Don't touch Sehyun.
Bastard.
If you want him to live,
then answer my questions properly.
What's your problem?
What exactly do you want?
Okay.
Kneel.
What?
I told you to kneel.
Then I'll consider
whether or not to kill him.
Sung Ho.
Don't do it. Just go.
I'll count to 3.
1,
2...
An ace cop—
have you no pride?
Hey.
Hey!
Take off your clothes.
What?
I said take off your clothes.
I have to see
if you have any listening devices on you.
Hey, you have a nice body.
No wonder he likes you.
All right.
Take off your belt.
Didn't you hear me?
Don't do it.
I said take off your belt.
Okay, next.
Tie your hands.
I said tie your hands.
Don't.
Don't...
Didn't you hear me?
Hands—
tie them up.
Hey, damn, you're so good at this.
All right.
Now crawl over here.
Crawl over like a dog.
Hey, Sung Ho, don't.
I said don't do it!
Hey.
Shut up.
Keep going.
Okay, that's enough.
You must be thinking, why is this bastard
humiliating me so much, right?
Then let me tell you.
You can't protect anyone—
including yourself,
and the people you want to protect.
Shut up!
Got it.
Look up.
Now tell me,
your family's secret.
I don't know.
What is the relationship between
your father and Assemblyman Zhao?
Tell me.
I left home in high school, I don't know.
Left home in high school?
Sounds quite real.
Then did you
leave home voluntarily?
Didn't your father pave the way
for you to become a cop?
I got in on my own.
Damn it!
Okay.
Then walk out of here yourself.
Hey, Sehyun.
The guy who said he'd save you
is kneeling and crawling here. Damn it.
This is the guy you chose.
Got it?
Kwon Hyukjae.
You're inhuman.
I got to where I am today thanks to that.
Sung Ho.
I'll ask you one last time.
Are you not going to give me
the information?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's keep playing then.
Sung Ho.
Sung Ho, save me!
Enough!
What?
Ready to change your mind?
Then speak.
What can you give me?
I'll tell you.
Okay.
Come on.
Tell me.
The information...
Who's there?
It's me,
Kim Minho.
O-Officer.
This isn't right.
Sung Ho is one of us.
This is crossing the line.
What?
Arresting him will solve this.
It shouldn't be coming to this.
Hey.
Are you trying to teach me what to do?
That's not it.
This is really dangerous!
Minho.
Didn't you say
you wanted to climb to the top?
That's why I paved the way for you!
But now you're playing the good guy,
you jerk.
I do want to climb to the top.
But...
It shouldn't be this way.
Damn it.
All right then.
You tell me.
How should we resolve this now?
Hey.
Kiss him.
Huh?
Don't you want to climb to the top?
You two figure it out.
If you don't kiss him, Sung Ho,
he'll die.
[Sin and Love]